emel.com 2019-02-11

# Privacy Policy | emel - the muslim lifestyle magazine

#### 1\. emel magazine’s commitment to privacy 

This is a legal document which sets out how emel magazine handles data which identifies you. You should read it in conjunction with the emel magazine Terms and Conditions, of which this Privacy Policy forms part.

At emel magazine, we believe strongly in protecting the privacy of our users’ personal information. This statement describes the privacy practices we apply for the emel magazine Service either through subscription or through emel.com. As part of that, it also expresses our approach to complying with the data protection laws which apply in the United Kingdom. If we change this Privacy Policy we will post the changes on this page and may place notices on other pages of the website, so that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it at all times.

At emel.com we collect different types of information about our users for three main reasons: 

1\. To help us to monitor and improve [replica cartier watches](http://www.cheapswiss.org/swiss-made-ladies-men-iwc.html) the services we offer.   
2\. To provide personalised services unique to individual users.   
3\. To use anonymous details about our users to sell appropriate advertising space on the site. This might mean showing an advertiser how many users we have on the site; it does not mean sharing an individual's details with an advertiser. Where we collect registration information from an individual, we will never share that individual's information with a third party, including an advertiser, without that user's explicit permission.   
If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement please contact us by email at [info@emel.com](mailto:info@emel.com).

#### 2\. Information gathered on registration 

When you register to use some the services of emel.com you provide us with your name, email, country and a password ("Registration Information"); if you register for  the paid  subscription service for the emel magazine you provide your name, address, telephone number, email address, credit or debit card details and some optional notes about yourself ("Registration Information"). If you wish to change any or all of your details please contact us using our email address at [info@emel.com](mailto:info@emel.com) or our postal address at emel magazine, 1 Canfield Place, London NW6 3BT.

#### 3\. Credit Card information 

All your payment details are processed through a secure payment system provided by Worldpay Plc. For further information about Worldpay Plc and its services, terms and conditions visit [www.worldpay.com](http://www.worldpay.com/)

#### 4\. Security

We have security measures in place to protect our customer database and access to this database is restricted internally. However, it remains each Member’s responsibility:(i) to ensure against use by anyone else of the emel magazine Service through the machine that Member uses while they are "logged on" to the emel magazine Service;(ii) to log off or exit from the emel magazine Service when not using it; and (iii) to keep his/her membership number and details secret.

#### 5\. Opt-out policy 

You may have your registration details removed at any time. To remove yourself please email at [info@emel.com](mailto:info@emel.com) and we will remove all your personal information contained in Your Details.

#### 6\. Disclosure for legal reasons 

We reserve the right to communicate such of a Member’s personal information as we hold to third parties which seek the disclosure of it, and which make a legally-compliant request for its disclosure.

#### 7\. Contacting emel magazine 

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with emel magazine, you can contact us at [info@emel.com](mailto:info@emel.com). You can also use our postal address specified above if you wish to request from emel magazine a copy of the personal data we hold about you or a description of that data. Please note that by English law we are entitled to charge you a small sum for providing this information.

####  8\. Data Protection Information 

You can obtain further information about data protection laws by visiting the Information Commissioner’s website at www.dataprotection.gov.uk. You can search for our Data Protection Notification there, should you so wish.

#### Last updated 10th June 2009  
© 2009 emel magazine. All rights reserved.
